<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bargsteen</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bargsteen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Misadventuring, hobo-style! // Bye Bye Dei</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/nine/</guid>
      <description>Misadventuring, hobo-style! // Bye Bye Dei 18&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Nine We looked up the rules for sleeping in parks in Nice. It was illegal. We did it anyway. Desperate times calls for tents in parks! A weird sound woke us up, sort of a &amp;lsquo;clunk clunk&amp;rsquo;. What the hell is that?! Turned out that our park was filled with petanque fields, and the sound came from an early bird training his skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Nice here</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/eight/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Nice here 17&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Eight It was melting hot day to hitchhike in, and maybe that&amp;rsquo;s why we failed. Wait what!? Yes, our semi-boiling brains gave in to the temptation of BlaBlaCar. Sorry to disappoint, but we had good a reason - Herbie Hancock was playing in Nice! We had bought tickets a few days before and were ready to end our trip with a jazzy explosion of augmented chords, improvisation and a Nice atmosphere (sorry for the pun :b).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffets and Beaches</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/seven/</guid>
      <description>Buffets and Beaches 16&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Seven Woke up in Irene&amp;rsquo;s rather humid house ready for a peachy beach adventure. Plenty of videos to go along, so I&amp;rsquo;ll keep my rambling ramblings short. Enjoy!
 Breakfast with our lovely host, Irene      Taking stock of the surroundings      Already drunk..    Diama staring into the glaring sun, as the sea settles    A hopeful fisherman preparing for throw-out    Woh Ouh, this ain&amp;#39;t good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hold on, Marseille! We&#39;re coming over</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/six/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/six/</guid>
      <description>Hold on, Marseille! We&amp;rsquo;re coming over 15&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Six Sleeping with your friends by the lake, doesn&amp;rsquo;t that just sound idyllic? Like something out of a fairy tale about two guys hitchhiking to France.
I woke up with a mild hangover and sneaked out of the tent. The others were still asleep, and I went for a morning swim in the lovely water. A little later, our friends, the strangers, cooked us a nice breakfast and brewed some extremely strong coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our friends, the Strangers</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/five/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/five/</guid>
      <description>Our friends, the strangers 14&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Five Hitchhiking doesn&amp;rsquo;t always go as planned, but, hopefully, there is joy waiting for you in the unknown. This is the story of how a hot and unlucky (hitchhiking wise) start in Paris turned into a row joyous encounters. It all started out with us leaving our hostel in the morning. Hopeful and sweaty we walked towards the highway. Our plan was simple: let&amp;rsquo;s go south!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I can has wine!?</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/four/</guid>
      <description>I can has wine!? 13&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Four Slighty hungover, we managed to get out of our lovely private hotel room and down to one of the best-rated cafés for brunch. Plane tickets were bought (yes we are cheating on our way back, but more about that later), food digested and coffee drunk. Then we moved onto discovering the city. We found the Luxembourg Park, which was quite nice and relaxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris, my Paris!</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/three/</guid>
      <description>Paris, my Paris! 12&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Three Today was a wild day. We slept in a park, went to Paris, drank, ate, saw, and photographed! The videoes and photos explain it quite well, so I&amp;rsquo;ll let them do most of the talking this time around. As they say: &amp;ldquo;A picture is worth a thousand words&amp;rdquo;, and those videos are 2:05 minutes long in total. Which means 125 seconds &amp;#42; 30 frames per sec &amp;#42; 1000 words per pic = 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh hey doggie!</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 15:07:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/two/</guid>
      <description>Oh hey doggie! 11&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter Two Boy, did we have an interesting night!? Dogs running into the side of the tent, drunk Germans, and bright and early runners. It had it all, to say the least, but we slept none the less. I, Dizzy, woke up before Diama and took a little video explaining my thoughts and actions to come. So here it comes. Video content, as promised. (Dizzys and Diamas always pay their debts (and keep their promises).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aalborg to Hannover in One Ride!</title>
      <link>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 15:07:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/misadventures-of-dizzy-and-diama/one/</guid>
      <description>Aalborg to Hannover in One Ride! 10&amp;frasl;07 - Chapter One This is the story, or misadventure if you will, of two unlikely comrades and their travels from the cold and rainy land of Denmark to the far warmer and sunny land of France. The heroes of this story are Kasper &amp;lsquo;Dizzy&amp;rsquo; Dissing Bargsteen and Deimantas &amp;lsquo;Diama&amp;rsquo; Jurevičius.
 Kasper &amp;#39;Dizzy&amp;#39; Dissing Bargsteen    Deimantas &amp;#39;Diama&amp;#39; Jurevičius   We started off in Aalborg around noon, and we quickly found a car going south.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>